Those things really led me to the clarity that neither of these parties are for the actual betterment of society, be it in the United States or internationally.
And by the way, I'm really happy that you, you know, you criticize both sides, Democrats, Republicans, equally, because all of them are not for black people.
Trash.
Have you always voted on one side?
I was always a Democrat because that's always what you're told to be as a black person.
And I also fell for the Obama, Obamaganda, etc.
I mean, but again, before the Internet and before the ability, the availability of all this information, you're really just getting your information from mainstream media.
And if you don't know any better, you think mainstream media is objective.
It is not.
And so for me, the real, real turning point was after October 7th and just watching simultaneously the truth happening on my phone, being spoken from the voices of Palestinians in real time.
And then seeing the lies being voiced by Kamala Harris, by Anthony Blinken, by Matthew Miller, by Joseph Biden and by mainstream media, you're seeing the two side by side, like how we're sitting here side by side was just I mean, there's no arguing after that.
There's nothing to actually try to figure out the proof, the proof, the proof is in the pudding.
It's in front of you.
And so, you know, once I also saw the willingness of Democrats to continue to fund Israel and this genocide, it allowed me to once and for all, you know, disassociate from them.
And then there was a whole smear campaign that black Democrats had against me on the Internet for challenging Kamala Harris to actually go against the genocide, not only because it's wrong, but also because if there was going to be any opportunity for her to garner a long lasting support because she was never going to win because it was rigged from the beginning.
She was never going to win. But if there was going to be any opportunity for her to have long lasting support, it was going to be for her to engage with the left, not the centrists.
And Democrats have actively ignored socialists, communists and leftists, even though those of us on the left are always advocating for simply collective liberation and for folks to have access to the basic needs of life and to stop prioritizing corporations.
So those things really led me to the clarity that neither of these parties are for the actual betterment of society, be it in the United States or internationally.
And then you start going down rabbit holes and paths and you really you really realize that it's always been this way.
They're just really good at PR. And so, you know, when when Hillary Clinton and these other Zionists say, you know, it's social media that is ruining our kids.
Well, they're right to a certain extent. They're ruining our kids ability to be brainwashed by them.
That's what's going to be.
The truth is becoming so much louder than the lie.